William Hobart Royce Papers
William Hobart Royce Papers
- Printed material
  - Anonymous or unknown authors, A-Z by article title or topic
    - "Balzac House Saved" (Royce catalog number: R1795) (Box 1)
    - "Les Balzaciens en Amérique"/"Une exposition Balzac" (Box 1)
    - "Balzac in England" (Royce catalog number: R1449) (Box 1)
    - "Balzac in English" (Royce catalog number: R3452) (Box 1)
    - "Balzac in Undress" (Royce catalog number: R1577) (Box 1)
    - "Balzac unconnu" (Box 1)
    - "Balzac jugé par Balzac" (Box 1)
    - "The Balzac Letters Controversy"/"Balzac Intime" (Royce catalog number: R1427) (Box 1)
    - "Balzac Love Letters Found in Ukraine" (Box 1)
    - (M., O.G.), "Balzac, marchand de bois" (Box 1)
    - "A Balzac Museum" (Royce catalog number: R1486) (Box 1)
    - "The Balzac Museum" (Royce catalog number: R1483) (Box 1)
    - "Balzac nous dît comment on mangeait au temps de Rastignac" (Box 1)
    - "Balzac observateur" (Box 1)
    - "Balzac, peintre de Paris" (Box 2)
    - "Balzac - regény a Peste Naplóban. Modeste Mignon" (Box 2)
    - "Balzac roturier; un ermite de lettres" (Box 2)
    - "Balzac saisi," in Le Figaro (Box 2)
    - "Balzac saisi," in Paris-Journal (Box 2)
    - "The Balzac 'skeleton'" (Royce catalog number: R1938) (Box 2)
    - "Balzac's Relations with Madame Hanska" (Box 2)
    - "Balzac's View of Women" (Box 2)
    - "Balzac Wrote Part of Stories on Proof" (Royce catalog number: R1509) (Box 2)
    - "Balzaciana" (Royce catalog number: R1936) (Box 2)
    - (M., Ch.), "Un Balzacien" (Box 2)
    - "Balzacien, M. Auriol?" Announcement of the new edition of Balzac, "L'Œuvre de Balzac" (Royce catalog number: S2475A/S2475B) (Box 2)
    - "Balzac's Climaxes" (Royce catalog number: R1481) (Box 2)
    - "Balzac's Country Doctor" (Royce catalog number: R1536) (Box 2)
    - "Balzac's Eugénie Grandet" (Royce catalog number: R1600) (Box 2)
    - "Balzac's La Comédie humaine, A Daughter of Eve, and Letters of Two Brides" (Box 2)
    - "Balzac's Perfumer" (The Nation) (Royce catalog number: R1777) (Box 2)
    - "Balzac's Perfumer" (New York Evening Post) (Box 2)
    - "Balzac Tried Everything Once" (Box 2)
    - "Balzac's Two Brothers and Alkahest" (Royce catalog number: R1537) (Box 2)
    - "Balzac's Vogue in America" (Royce catalog number: R1657) (Box 2)
    - "Bookwright" (Box 2)
    - "Boro Man, resembling Balzac, Eager Collector of His Works" (Box 2)
    - "Brunetière's Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1664) (Box 2)
    - "Buys Balzac Manuscript" (Royce catalog number: R1800) (Box 2)
    - "Le Candidat-Omnibus" (Royce catalog number: R1504a) (Box 2)
    - "La canne de Balzac" (Paris-Journal) (Box 2)
    - "La canne de Balzac" (Siècle) (Box 2)
    - "Cast of Balzac's Hand Given to Paris Museum" (Box 2)
    - "Ce qu'on voyait de chez Balzac" (Box 2)
    - "Cem anos depois… Os [sic] últimos momentos de Balzac vistos por Victor Hugo" (Box 2)
    - "Les cent jours de H. de Balzac" (Box 2)
    - "Les cent visages de Balzac" (Box 2)
    - "Le centenaire de Balzac" (Box 2)
    - "Le centenaire de Balzac imprimeur" (Box 2)
    - "Le centenaire de la mort de Balzac" (Box 2)
    - "Le centenaire du Romantisme à Issoudun" (Box 2)
    - "El centenario de Balzac" (Box 2)
    - "The Centennial of Balzac's Birth" (Royce catalog number: R1477) (Box 2)
    - "Les champs de bataille de l'Empire" (Royce catalog number: R1502k) (Box 2)
    - "Chez les Balzaciens d'Amérique" (Box 2)
    - "Chronique bibliographique ... Lettres à l'Étrangère, Tome III" (Box 2)
    - "The Clinical Significance of Balzac's Death from Overwork" (Royce catalog number: R1569) (Box 2)
    - "Comédie Humaine..." (Royce catalog number: R1450) (Box 2)
    - "La Comédie humaine - Oeuvres complètes de M. H. De Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1502) (Box 2)
    - (L., Ed.), "Comme quoi avant dix-huits cents ans, un conte de M. De Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1502a) (Box 2)
    - "Commemoration of Balzac Centenary at Bristol" (Box 2)
    - "Concerning the Maison Vauquer of Balzac's le Père Goriot" (Royce catalog number: R1479) (Box 2)
    - "La conférence du 3 Février à l'Alliance Française" (Box 2)
    - "Un congrès plusieurs pèlerinages et des expositions vont marquer l'année Balzac" (Royce catalog number: S2939a) (Box 2)
    - "Conjecture on Balzac's 150th Birthday (Royce catalog number: S2980a) (Box 2)
    - "Contes bruns, par une tête à l'envers" (Royce catalog number: R1875) (Box 2)
    - [Reeve, Henry?]"The Correspondence of H. De Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1593) (Box 2)
    - "The Costumes of the Comédie Humaine" (Royce catalog number: R1772) (Box 2)
    - "Courrier des lettres: Balzac et l'Étrangère" (Box 2)
    - "Création artistique et vie religieuse chez Balzac" (Box 3)
    - "Critic and Author" (Royce catalog number: R1429) (Box 3)
    - "Les 'Culottes de bois' de Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1619) (Box 3)
    - "La culture Français dans les Démocraties populaires, Balzac en Hongrie" (Box 3)
    - "Dans le genre de Balzac" (Box 3)
    - "Daniel Stone's Portraits Unveiled at 'Les Jardins' [sic]" (Box 3)
    - "The Death of Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1457) (Box 3)
    - "De Balzac à Vautel" (Box 3)
    - "Une dedicace de Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1614) (Box 3)
    - "Le Dernier Chouan on le Bretagne en 1800, par M. Honoré Balzac (Royce catalog number: S3344A) (Box 3)
    - "Des descendants de Balzac" (Box 3)
    - "Deux reliques de Balzac" (Box 3)
    - "De Vermeer à Balzac" (Box 3)
    - "Les dix mille élégances de M. De Balzac" (Box 3)
    - "D'un nouvel obscurcissement de l'horizon du cot de oriental sou..." (Royce catalog number: R1502g) (Box 3)
    - "Décolleté des ménage. Le theatre romanticism à l'Odéon" (Box 3)
    - "The English Balzac" (Box 3)
    - "Inveiglement du secateurs Clément de Ris et la tribunal d'Angers: Histoire et legende (1801)" (Box 3)
    - "An Episode under the Terror" (Box 3)
    - "Erection place de Palais-Royal de la statue de Balzac" (Box 3)
    - "Essai, jusqu'au 31 décembre 1894, d'une bibliographie des lettres d'Honoré de Balzac parues dans les journaux, les recueils et les volumes." (Royce catalog number: R2949) (Box 3)
    - (G.,L.; G.E. [= Guinot, Eugène?]), "Etudes litteraires. Oeuvres de M. De Balzac - La Fleur des Pois" (Royce catalog number: R1502b) (Box 3)
    - "Eugénie Grandet's home: the pension Vauquer" (Royce catalog number: R1487) (Box 3)
    - "Eugène Sue" (Box 3)
    - (K., R.), "Eugénie Grandet à l'Odèon" (Box 3)
    - "Uma Exposiçâo Consagrada à vida e à obra de Balzac" (Box 3)
    - "Une exposition Balzac" (Box 3)
    - "The Extraordinary Author of the Human Comedy" (Box 3)
    - "A Famous Controversy Ended" (Box 3)
    - "Famous Courtship by Mail Ended in Marriage, but too late" (Box 3)
    - "Famous Love Letters: Balzac to Countess Hanska" (Box 3)
    - "Les femmes et l'amour dans l'oeuvre de Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1617) (Box 3)
    - "Ferry's Balzac", "Lettres à l'Étrangère", "The Best of Balzac", Honoré de Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1774, R1775, R1776, R1778) (Box 3)
    - "Les Fêtes du Centenaire du Romantisme à Issoudun" (Box 3)
    - "Feu Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1681) (Box 3)
    - "Food and letter" (Royce catalog number: R1796) (Box 3)
    - "A memoir of Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1817) (Box 3)
    - "The France of Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1502) (Box 3)
    - "French Novels: de Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1734) (Box 3)
    - "French Town Honors Balzac Student Here" (Box 3)
    - "From Hackwork to Masterpieces: Balzac and the 'Comédie Humaine" (Royce catalog number: R1668) (Box 3)
    - "Funérailles d'Honoré de Balzac" (Box 3)
    - "The Genius of Rodin" (Royce catalog number: R1566) (Box 3)
    - "Un gilet de Balzac" (Box 3)
    - "Goriot apó" (Box 3)
    - "Gozlan's Balzac en pantoufles" (Royce catalog number: R1781) (Box 3)
    - "Un grand centenaire" (Box 3)
    - "Graphologue en defaut" (Box 3)
    - (G., D.), "Guide to Balzac" (Box 3)
    - "Henri de Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1573) (Box 3)
    - "Mr. Henry James on Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1492) (Box 3)
    - "Honor of the Family - Balzac to Broadway" (Royce catalog number: R1801) (Box 3)
    - "Honorato de Balzac" (Box 3)
    - "Honoré Balzac" (Box 3)
    - "Honoré Balzac" (Box 3)
    - "Honoré de Balzac," in Basler Volksblatt (Box 3)
    - "Honoré de Balzac," in Bentley's Miscellany (Royce catalog number: R1458) (Box 3)
    - "Honoré de Balzac," in Die Barke (Box 3)
    - "Honoré de Balzac à Minerva: M. Le professeur Sentou évoque sa pensée politique et sociale" (Box 3)
    - "Honoré de Balzac. Charmante conférence de M. Marcel Bouteron" (Box 4)
    - "Honoré de Balzac," "Il y a 100 ans le (futur) cinéma comptait (dêjà) six scénaristes" (Box 4)
    - "Honoré de Balzac: The Interpreter of Life" (Box 4)
    - "Honoré de Balzac, premier president de la Société des Gens de Lettres" (Box 4)
    - "Honoré de Balzac," in The Saturday Review (Royce catalog number: R1904) (Box 4)
    - "Honoré de Balzac," in Harper's New Monthly Magazine (Royce catalog number: R1655) (Box 4)
    - "Honoré de Balzac," in Temple Bar (Royce catalog number: R1918) (Box 4)
    - "Honoré de Balzac, par M. Théophile Gautier" (Royce catalog number: R1857) (Box 4)
    - "Husbands, Build You with Care to Keep Your Wives Faithful" (Box 4)
    - "L'illumination d'Honoré de Balzac" (Box 4)
    - "L'illustre Gaudissart" (Box 4)
    - "Inauguration du monument élevé à la mémoire d'Honoré de Balzac" (Box 4)
    - "Inauguration du monument de Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1929) (Box 4)
    - (F., E.0), "L'inauguration du monument de Balzac" (Box 4)
    - "Inauguration d'une plaque à la Maison de Balzac" (Box 4)
    - "Inauguration d'un portrait en marble de Balzac..." (Box 4)
    - "Une inauguration en l'honneur de Balzac" (Box 4)
    - (S., A.), "Indiscrétions littéraires. M. De Balzac" (Box 4)
    - "Inexhaustible Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1802) (Box 4)
    - "Les journées Balzaciennes d'Alençon" (Box 4)
    - "Lettres à l'Étrangère..." (Royce catalog number: R1451) (Box 4)
    - "Une lettre et une protestation de Mme. De Balzac" (Box 4)
    - (E., M.V.), "Lettre sur la famille d'Honoré de Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R2533) (Box 4)
    - "Die Liebe führte ihn nach Wien..." (Box 4)
    - [unsigned, written by Hazletine, M.W.], "A Life of Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1793) (Box 4)
    - "Literary Pilgrimages at Home and Abroad VII. Aspects of Balzac's Paris" (Royce catalog number: R1785) (Box 4)
    - "Literary Relics of Balzac for U.S." (Box 4)
    - "Littérature. Jane la Pâle, Par H. De Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1502c) (Box 4)
    - "Le livre des 400 auteurs" (Box 4)
    - "Livres aux enchères" (Royce catalog number: R1716) (Box 4)
    - "Livres imprimés par Balzac" (Box 4)
    - "The love Affairs of Hugo and Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1565) (Box 4)
    - (S., G.V.), "Au Lycée Français de Bruxelles. Balzac en Images..." (Box 4)
    - "Madame de Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1485) (Box 4)
    - "M. De Balzac - Sa Revue parisienne-M. Victor Hugo jugé par Balzac" (Box 4)
    - "La maison de Balzac," in Annales (Box 4)
    - "A la maison de Balzac," in Excelsior (Box 4)
    - "La maison de Balzac," in Journal [?] (Box 4)
    - "La maison de Balzac," in Nouvelles Littéraires (Box 4)
    - "La maison de Balzac," in Paris-Journal (Box 4)
    - "A la maison de Balzac," in Paris-Journal, 23 Apr 1909 (Box 4)
    - "A la maison de Balzac," in Paris-Journal, 11 Nov 1910 (Box 4)
    - "La maison de Balzac est sauvée" (Box 4)
    - "La maison de Balzac et l'institut" (Box 4)
    - "La maison de Balzac de la rue Raynouard" (Box 4)
    - (P., M.), "La Maison de Balzac menacée" (Box 4)
    - "La Maison de Balzac nous sera conservée" (Box 4)
    - "La maison de Balzac. Une visite prochaine de M. M. Dujardin..." (Box 4)
    - "Le mariage de Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1683) (Box 4)
    - "Le mariage de M. de Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1504b) (Box 4)
    - "Maximes et pensées de Napoléon" (Box 4)
    - "M. de Balzac" (Box 4)
    - "A la mémoire de Balzac," in Paris-Journal, 1910 (Box 4)
    - "A la mémoire de Balzac," Paris-Journal, 1911 (Box 4)
    - "Metropolitan Provincialism" (Box 4)
    - "Mr. Royce Addresses Spectator Club at 1st Luncheon Meeting" (Box 4)
    - "Le mobilier de Balzac 'expulsé'" (Box 4)
    - "M. Grandet n'était pas le Roi des Avares!" (Box 4)
    - "Monsieur, Madame et Mademoiselle Grandet" (Box 4)
    - "M. Marc Eigeldenger parle de Balzac" (Box 4)
    - "M. Paul Bourget sur l'écran du cinéma" (Royce catalog number: R1583) (Box 4)
    - "M. Pierre Benoit et Balzac" (Box 4)
    - "The Morality of Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1844) (Box 4)
    - "Mort d'Honoré de Balzac" (Box 4)
    - "Mort de Surville de Balzac" (Box 4)
    - "Un musée de Balzac dans l'Amerique du Sud" (Box 4)
    - "Le Musée Balzac s'ouvrit, hier, à un petit groupe d'invités" (Box 4)
    - "Le Musée Balzac. Un homage au génie" (Box 4)
    - "le Musée Balzac a ouvert ses grilles..." (Box 4)
    - "Musée falling to decay" (Box 4)
    - "Musée Balzac Saved" (Royce catalog number: R2206) (Box 4)
    - "The Mythical Englishman" (Royce catalog number: R1491) (Box 4)
    - "Nécrologie: Joseph Gabalda" (Box 4)
    - "The New Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1490) (Box 5)
    - "New Light on the Tragic Life of Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1571) (Box 5)
    - (C., G.), "Un noble parrainage: Balzac père des bateaux parisiens" (Box 5)
    - "Notice and excerpt of Henri de Curzon's article on...Vautrin) (Box 5)
    - "Une nouvelle bibliographie de Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1615) (Box 5)
    - "Une nouvelle de Balzac: Le Sous-Préfet" (Box 5)
    - "Nouvelles Balzachinades" (Royce catalog number: R1502d) (Box 5)
    - "The Novel and its Art" (Royce catalog number: R1484) (Box 5)
    - "The Novel's Three giants" (Box 5)
    - "Obras de Balzac no Cinema" (Box 5)
    - "A l'Odeon. Une pièce inédite de Balzac..." (Box 5)
    - "L'Oeuvre de Balzac" (Box 5)
    - "Un parapluie d'occasion" (Box 5)
    - (M., H.), "A l'Opéra-Comique: 'la Peau de chagrin'," "La Maison de Balzac" (Box 5)
    - "Parmi la descendance de Balzac dans la vie et dans la fiction," "Ausuijet de Mme. De Balzac et de sa correspondance" (Royce catalog number: R1514, R1515) (Box 5)
    - "Paul Bourget balzacien" (Box 5)
    - "Peasant studies in French fiction" (Royce catalog number: R1595) (Box 5)
    - "Uma personagem Balzaciana: Honoré de Balzac" (Box 5)
    - "Un portrait de Balzac" (Box 5)
    - "Pour l'aménagement du site de la maison de Balzac" (Box 5)
    - "La première tragédie de Balzac" (Box 5)
    - "Un précieux manuscrit de Balzac" (Box 5)
    - "Programme," Tournées Ch. Baret 'Le Faiseur' [empty envelop] (Box 5)
    - "Private libraries ... Mr. Royce's Balzacian Collection Contains Many Rare Examples" (Royce catalog number: S2439A) (Box 5)
    - "À propos de Barbey d'Aurevilly et Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1616) (Box 5)
    - "Un projet de journal de J.-K. Huysmans. La Comédie humaine" (Box 5)
    - (C., A.M.), "A propos du centenaire de la mort de Balzac" (Box 5)
    - "Le Quinzaine Honoré de Balzac" (Box 5)
    - "Ramsey Assessor Owns World's Most Complete Set of Balzac" (Box 5)
    - "Rastignac 1946" (Box 5)
    - "La réalité et le réel dans Balzac" (Box 5)
    - "Recent French Literature" (Royce catalog number: R1913) (Box 5)
    - "Review of Balzac, 'La Femme Auteur' et autres fragments inédits"
    - Review of Benjamin, Balzac (Box 5)
    - (P., A.), Review of Evans Louis, "Lambert et la philosophie de Balzac" (Box 5)
    - (Bury, R. de), Review of Hanotaux et Vicàire, "Balzac imprimeur" (Royce catalog number: R1745) (Box 5)
    - Review of Saltus, "Balzac," "Balzac's Pere Goriot," "Cesar Birotteau" (Royce catalog number: R1700, R1701, R1702) (Box 5)
    - Review of Sanders, "Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1766) (Box 5)
    - Review of Second, "Essais sur Balzac par M. Paul Flat" (Royce catalog number: R1447) (Box 5)
    - Review of Lawton, "Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1660) (Box 5)
    - "Un Secret de Balzac" (Box 5)
    - Review of Serval, "Une amie de Balzac: Mme Marbouty" (Box 5)
    - Review of Seillière, "Balzac et la morale romantique" (Box 5)
    - Review of Zweig, "Balzac" (Box 5)
    - Review of "The Village Rector," Robert Bros. Edition (Royce catalog number: R1549) (Box 5)
    - "The Revived Interest in Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1478) (Box 5)
    - "Revue de Paris" (Box 5)
    - "Rodin's Balzac" (Box 5)
    - "Rodin Reflections Invited by a Group of His Bronces" (Box 5)
    - "Royce Finds Balzac Shakespeare's Peer" (Box 5)
    - "Sainte-Beuve and the Romantics" (Royce catalog number: R1594) (Box 5)
    - "Second-Théâtre-Français. Les Ressourices de Iuinola, par M. De Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1502i) (Box 5)
    - (S., A. [Second, Albéric]), "Le sire de Balzac dans sa terre de Villerglé" (Box 5)
    - "Une soirèe chez M. De Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1502h) (Box 5)
    - "Les sources d'un roman de Balzac" (Box 5)
    - "La statue de Balzac joue de Malheur" (Box 5)
    - "La statue de Balzac par Falguière" (Box 5)
    - [Fagel, André], "Les statues" (Royce catalog number: R1663) (Box 5)
    - "The Style of Balzac and Thackeray" (Box 5)
    - (P., C.), "Sur la gouvernante de Balzac...," "L'italien de Balzac" (Box 5)
    - "Swineburne's Debt to Balzac" (Box 5)
    - "Tales from Balzac" (Royce catalog number: R1937) (Box 5)
    - "Théâtre-Historique, La Marate" (Royce catalog number: R1505) (Box 5)
    - (S., G.), "Théâtres Parisiens...L'École des Ménages, au théâtre Saint-Georges" (Box 5)
    - "Topographie littéraire. Découverte de quelque grands hommes contemporains ..." (Royce catalog number: R1502e) (Box 5)
    - "Town in France Hails Balzac Bibliographer..." (Box 6)
    - "à travers le continent Balzacien" (Royce catalog number: R1618) (Box 6)
    - "À travers le passé. Les différents logis et petites habitudes d'un grand homme" (Box 6)
    - "El Triumfador del Condurso de Balzac Recibió sus Premios" (Box 6)
    - "The True Story of Balzac and Madame Hanska" (Royce catalog number: R1572) (Box 6)
    - "Two Literary Studies" (Royce catalog number: R1454) (Box 6)
    - "A Unique Treasure" (Royce catalog number: R1905) (Box 6)
    - (R., F.), "L'U.R.S.S. et Balzac" (Box 6)
    - "A vida de Balzac" (Box 6)
    - "La vie secrète des grandes amoureuses" (Box 6)
    - "Une vieille maison de Doude dans un roman de Balzac" (Box 6)
    - "Visite à Balzac" (Box 6)
    - Levaillant, Maurice, "La vocation de Balzac" (Box 6)
    - "Le vrai Vautrin" (Box 6)
  - Abbott, Lawrence F. [empty envelope] (Royce catalog number: R1400) (Box 6)
  - Abraham, Pierre (Box 6)
  - Adams, J. Donald (Box 6)
  - Adémar, Jean (Box 6)
  - Agate, James (Box 6)
  - Ageores, Joseph (Royce catalog number: R1407) (Box 6)
  - Alain (Box 6)
  - Alain; Bede, Jean-Albert; Bouteron, Marcel; Creyton, Helene; Descaves, Pierre; Estrangin, Guy; Messieres, René de; Ozenfant; Peyre, Henri; Royce, William Hobart; Stern, Alfred (Box 6)
  - Alain; Bourin, André; Bouteron, Marcel; Gallotti, Jean; Henriot, Emile; Kemp, Robert; Maurois, Andre; Romains, Jules (Box 6)
  - d'Alméras, Henri (Box 6)
  - d'Alméras, Henri (Royce catalog number: R1422) (Box 6)
  - Ambrière, [Francis] (Box 6)
  - Ambrière, Francis (Box 6)
  - Amyot, R.-T. (Box 6)
  - Andrieu, Paul-Léon; Chargelègue, Jack; Labbe, P.; Vannier, Daniel (Box 6)
  - Aparicio, Antonio (Box 6)
  - Aparicio, Antonio (Box 6)
  - Arbelet, Paul (Royce catalog number: R1947) (Box 6)
  - [d']Arghiavine, [René] (Box 6)
  - d'Ariste, Paul (Box 6)
  - Ariste, Jean-Paul (Box 6)
  - Arland, Marcel (Box 6)
  - Armory (Box 6)
  - Arnault, Eugène; Blaize, Jean; Charlety, Sébastien; Dévigne, Roger; Escholier, Raymond; Labadie, Jean; Lecomte, Georges (Box 6)
  - Arnold, Matthew (Royce catalog number: R1951) (Box 6)
  - Aruss, Arsène (Royce catalog number: R1952) (Box 6)
  - Arvad, Inga (Box 6)
  - Aubrée, Etienne (Box 6)
  - Auclair, Marcelle (Box 6)
  - Audiat, Pierre (Box 6)
  - Auriant (Box 6)
  - Avenal, Paul (Royce catalog number: S3418A) (Box 6)
  - Ayme, Marcel (Box 6)
  - Azorin (Box 6)
  - Bac, Ferdinand (Box 6)
  - Babelon, Jean (Box 6)
  - Bachlin, Henri (Royce catalog number: R1971) (Box 6)
  - Bachlin, Henri and Dumesnil, René (Royce catalog number: R1973, R1975, R1976, R1977 ) (Box 6)
  - Baer, Arthur "Bugs" (Box 7)
  - Baker, H. Barton (Royce catalog number: R1981) (Box 7)
  - Balducci, Luigi (Box 7)
  - Baldensberger, Fernand (Box 7)
  - Ballaguy, Paul (Royce catalog number: R1990) (Box 7)
  - Balzac, Honoré de, 4 folders (Box 7)
  - Balzac, Honoré de, La Cousine Bette et Les Deux Musiciens [first edition, publ. as a roman-feuilleton series in "Le Constitutionel"], 1846 (Oversize 2)
  - Balzac, Honoré de, Une Ténébreuse Affaire [reprint], 28 Jan 1941 (Oversize 5)
  - Balzac [the journal] #1-19 (Oversize 12)
  - Banville, Theodore de (Box 7)
  - Barbou, Alfred (Box 7)
  - Barbagelata, J.C. (Box 7)
  - Bareches, Francois (Box 7)
  - Barr, Jean de (Royce catalog number: R2008) (Box 7)
  - Barzun, Jacques (Box 7)
  - Basil, Otto (Box 7)
  - Billy, André & Maurois, André (Box 7)
  - Bauër, Gérard (Royce catalog number: R2019, R2020, R2021, R2022, R2023, R2024, R2025, R2026, R2029, R2030 ) (Box 7)
  - Bauer, Gilles (Box 8)
  - Beaumont, Germaine (Box 8)
  - Beaurepaire-Froment (Royce catalog number: R2039) (Box 8)
  - Becker, May Lamberton (Box 8)
  - Béguin, Albert (Box 8)
  - Béguin, Albert; Ducourneau, Jean A.; Hugo, Victor (Box 8)
  - Bell, Lisle (Box 8)
  - Bellaigne, Camille (Royce catalog number: R2042) (Box 8)
  - Bellessort, André (Royce catalog number: R2047, R2048) (Box 8)
  - Ben [cartoon] (Box 8)
  - Benda, Julien (Royce catalog number: R2051) (Box 8)
  - Benedict, Joan (Royce catalog number: R2052, R2053) (Box 8)
  - Benjamin, René (Royce catalog number: R2060, R2198 II-VI) (Box 8)
  - Benjamin, René; Bergner, Georges; Charensol, Georges; Chaucerel, André; Dullin, Charles; Fouchardière, G. De la; Gandon, Yves; Jollivet, S.; Néroman, D.; Le Scribe Accroupi; Vindex (Box 8)
  - Bennett, Arnold (Box 8)
  - Bernard, Gabriel (Box 8)
  - Bernheim, Adrien (Box 8)
  - Bernoville, Gastan (Box 8)
  - Berry, Marion (Box 8)
  - Bersaucourt, Albert de (Royce catalog number: R2071, R2073) (Box 8)
  - Bertaut, Jules (Box 8)
  - Bertault, Philippe (Box 8)
  - Bertrand, Jules (Royce catalog number: R2075, R2076, R2077, R2079, R2080, R2081, R2088, R2089, R2090 ), 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Berthier, Pierre-Valentin (Box 9)
  - Bicho, Jocelyn Guttmann (Box 9)
  - Bidou, Henry (Box 9)
  - Bienstock, J.-W. (Royce catalog number: R2111) (Box 9)
  - Biez, Jacques de (Royce catalog number: R2114, R2115, R2116) (Box 9)
  - Billy, André (Royce catalog number: R2120) (Box 9)
  - Biré, Edmond (Royce catalog number: R151, R2122, R2124, R2125, R2135 ) (Box 9)
  - Blanc, Francisque (Box 9)
  - Blei, Franz (Royce catalog number: R2140) (Box 9)
  - Block, Louis J. (Royce catalog number: R2141) (Box 9)
  - Boissy, Gabriel (Royce catalog number: R2145) (Box 9)
  - Bonneau, Alcide (Royce catalog number: R2146) (Box 9)
  - Bordeaux, Henry (Royce catalog number: R2158, R2159, R2161) (Box 9)
  - Botrot, Jean (Box 9)
  - Botrot, Jean et alii, in Noveades (Box 9)
  - Bougiovanni, Giannetto (Box 9)
  - Boulé, Alphonse (Royce catalog number: R181) (Box 9)
  - Bourges, Ernest (Box 9)
  - Bourget, Paul (Royce catalog number: R2185) (Box 9)
  - Bourget, Paul (Royce catalog number: R2172, R2178, R2184, R2189) (Box 10)
  - Bournon, Fernand (Box 10)
  - Boussel, Patrice (Box 10)
  - Bouteron, Marcel (Royce catalog number: R198, R1496, R2200, R2202, R2203, R2204, R2207, R2208, R2209, R2210, R2211, R2212, R2213, S3724 ), 3 folders (Box 10)
  - Boy-Zelénski, Thadée (Box 10)
  - Bozd, Ernest (Royce catalog number: R2219) (Box 10)
  - Boynton, H.W. (Royce catalog number: R2220) (Box 10)
  - Brami, Me Edmond (Box 10)